Guide to the James Marshall Osborn Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Box and Folder List, 1960
  - Miner, Earl, 1957-75 (Box 53, Folder 1107)
    UCLA, Princeton, Dryden, etc.
  - Mizener, Arthur, 1939-54 (Box 53, Folder 1108)
    Yale, Cornell
  - Modern Humanities Research Association, 1938-76 (Box 53, Folder 1109)
  - Modern Language Association, 1940-75 (Box 53, Folder 1110)
  - Monk, Samuel Holt, 1951-64 (Box 53, Folder 1111)
    University of Minnesota, Dryden
  - Montgomery, Lee, 1934-39 (Box 53, Folder 1112)
    Cousin of Mrs. Osborn
  - Moore, John Robert, 1940-71 (Box 54, Folder 1113)
    Indiana University, Dryden, Luttrell, etc.
  - Moore, Will G., 1940-42 (Box 54, Folder 1114)
    St. John's College, Oxford, Work in Progress and MHRA
  - Morgan, Peter F., 1966-67 (Box 54, Folder 1115)
    Hood
  - Morgan Guaranty Trust Co., 1966-69 (Box 54, Folder 1116)
  - Morison, Samuel Eliot, 1887-197?, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 1117)
  - Morris, Brian R., 1960-63 (Box 54, Folder 1118)
    Cleveland
  - Mortlake, Harold, & Co., 1959-60 (Box 54, Folder 1119)
  - Morton, Richard E., 1956-76 (Box 54, Folder 1120)
    McMaster, Cokagne
  - Mossner, Ernest C., 1931-68 (Box 54, Folder 1121)
    Columbia, Texas, 18th century etc.
  - Mott, Howard S., 1956-64 (Box 54, Folder 1122)
  - Motter, Vail, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 1123)
  - Muirhead, Arnold, 1952-67 (Box 54, Folder 1124)
  - Mullins, E. L. C., 1971 (Box 54, Folder 1125)
    History of Parliament Trust
  - Munby, Alan Noel Latimer, 1913-1974, 1951-73 (Box 54, Folder 1126)
    King's College Librarian, Cambridge
  - Mundie, Elizabeth, 1944 (Box 54, Folder 1127)
    Family friend
  - Mundy, Percy C. Dryden, 1939-59 (Box 54, Folder 1128-1129)
  - Munhall, Edgar, 1964-67 (Box 54, Folder 1130)
  - Murtfeldt, Edward W., 1957-64 (Box 54, Folder 1131)
    Wesleyan '28 and Columbia
  - The Museum of Modern Art, 1947-66 (Box 54, Folder 1132)
  - Myers & Co. Ltd., 1940-75 (Box 55, Folder 1133-1139)
  - Myers, Vernon C., 1956-68 (Box 55, Folder 1140)
  - Myres, J. Nowell L., 1955-68 (Box 55, Folder 1141-1142)
    Bodley's librarian
  - Myres, M. Timothy, 1964-65 (Box 55, Folder 1143)
    Biologist, Alberta (son of J. N. L.)
  - Nadel, George H., 1963-67 (Box 56, Folder 1144)
  - Namier, Sir Lewis B., 1953 Sep 2 (Box 56, Folder 1145)
    Parliamentary history
  - Nangle, Benjamin Christie, 1938-72 (Box 56, Folder 1146)
  - National Library of Scotland, 1949-62 (Box 56, Folder 1147)
  - National Municipal League, 1957-72 (Box 56, Folder 1148)
  - National Portrait Gallery, 1940-75 (Box 56, Folder 1149)
  - National Register of Archives (Scotland), 1963 (Box 56, Folder 1150)
    Stair MSS
  - National Research Council (Panel on Underwater Swimmers), 1951-54 (Box 56, Folder 1151)
    Rabbards frogman
  - Neale, Sir John E., 1959-60 (Box 56, Folder 1152)
    The Passage of Her Majesty [Queen Elizabeth]
  - Nebenzahl, Kenneth, Inc., 1962 (Box 56, Folder 1153)
  - Needham, Francis, 1936-37 (Box 56, Folder 1154)
    Dryden and Malone
  - Neill, Desmond G., 1950-66 (Box 56, Folder 1155)
    Lady Winchilsea, Malone, Bodleian
  - Nelson, Lowry, 1970-76 (Box 56, Folder 1156)
    Yale Comparative Literature
  - Nethercot, Arthur H., 1952 (Box 56, Folder 1157)
    Cowley
  - New Haven Citizen's Committee for Council-Mayor Charter, Inc., 1949-63 (Box 56, Folder 1158)
  - New Haven Free Public Library, 1958-76 (Box 56, Folder 1159)
  - New Haven Preservation Trust, 1962-66 (Box 56, Folder 1160)
  - New Haven Symphony Orchestra, 1969-74 (Box 56, Folder 1161)
  - New Haven Taxpayers Research Council, 1951-58 (Box 56, Folder 1162)
  - New York Public Library, 1940-68 (Box 56, Folder 1163)
  - The New York Times, 1952-65 (Box 56, Folder 1164)
  - Newman, Julia Sweet, 1963-67 (Box 56, Folder 1165)
  - Nicholes, Eleanor Louise, 1958-65 (Box 56, Folder 1166)
    Pforzheimer Library
  - Nichols, J. Alden, 1941-50 (Box 56, Folder 1167)
    Wesleyan undergraduate
  - Nicoll, Allardyce, 1938-71 (Box 56, Folder 1168)
  - Nicolson, Marjorie, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 1169)
  - Nitchie, Elizabeth, 1949-50 (Box 56, Folder 1170)
    Goucher, English Inst.
  - Noble, Yvonne, 1966-70 (Box 56, Folder 1171)
    Elizabeth Graeme Fergusson
  - Norton, Jane E., 1959-60 (Box 56, Folder 1172)
    Edward Gibbon
  - Norton, Paul F., 1957-58 (Box 56, Folder 1173)
    Latrobe
  - Noss, Luther and Osea, 1960-61 (Box 56, Folder 1174)
    Yale School of Music
  - Notestein, Wallace, 1939-68 (Box 56, Folder 1175)
    Yale Historian
  - Nottingham Library, University of, 1950-68 (Box 56, Folder 1176)
  - Novak, Max, 1970-75 (Box 56, Folder 1177)
    UCLA, Dryden, etc.
  - Noyes, George R., 1936-52 (Box 56, Folder 1178)
    Berkley, Dryden
  - Oakes, Norman E., 1956-61 (Box 57, Folder 1179)
    Ralph Griffiths
  - Oakshot, Walter, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1180)
  - Oates, J. C. T., 1957 (Box 57, Folder 1181)
    Cambridge, editor, The Library
  - Ober, William B., M. D., 1968-69 (Box 57, Folder 1182)
    English writers and Mahler
  - O'Farrell, Nellie McNeill, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 1183)
    Ralph Rabbards
  - O'Flaherty, Patrick, 1962-63 (Box 57, Folder 1184)
    John Pinkerton
  - O'Hehir, Brendan P., 1962-70 (Box 57, Folder 1185)
    Berkely, Denham, etc.
  - O'Keefe Daniel L., 1968-69 (Box 57, Folder 1186)
  - Oldman, C. B., 1954-68 (Box 57, Folder 1187)
  - O'Neill, William B., 1972-73 (Box 57, Folder 1188)
  - Oras, Ants, 1936-69 (Box 57, Folder 1189)
    University of Florida, English Inst., etc.
  - Ortner, Peter B., 1967-69 (Box 57, Folder 1190)
    Yale '70, student assistant in Osborn Collection
  - Osborn, Arthur Herbert, 1884-, 1955-58 (Box 57, Folder 1191)
    Cousin
  - Osborn, Merle M., d. 1975, 1938-75 (Box 57, Folder 1192)
  - Osterweis, Rollin G., 1964-74 (Box 57, Folder 1193)
    Yale historian and friend
  - O'Sullivan, William, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 1194)
    Trinity College, Dublin, candidate for research assistant
  - O'Toole, John H., 1935-64 (Box 57, Folder 1195)
  - Ottemiller, John H., 1955-67 (Box 57, Folder 1196)
    Associate Librarian, Yale University Library
  - Owen, Charles, 1969-74 (Box 57, Folder 1197)
    University of Connecticut, English Inst., National Municipal League
  - Oxford University, 1937-68 (Box 57, Folder 1198)
  - Oxford University Press, 1939-68 (Box 57, Folder 1199-1201)
  - Oxford University Press (New York), 1950-66 (Box 57, Folder 1202)
  - Pafford, J. H. P., 1951-65 (Box 58, Folder 1203)
    University of London Library
  - Paget, Hugh, 1910-, 1936-39 (Box 58, Folder 1204-1206)
    Periodical Index
  - Palfrey, Thomas R., 1941-47 (Box 58, Folder 1207)
    Northwestern
  - Palmer, John, 1955-70 (Box 58, Folder 1208)
    Dean, Silliman College, editor, Yale Review
  - Palmer, Rupert E., Jr., 1965-70 (Box 58, Folder 1209)
    Vanderbilt, Whythorne
  - Papantonio, Michael, d. 1978, 1957-64 (Box 58, Folder 1210)
    Bookseller, Seven Gables Bookshop
  - Pargellis, Stanley, 1946-62 (Box 58, Folder 1211)
    Newberry Library
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, Inc., 1941-60 (Box 58, Folder 1212)
  - Parker, William Riley, 1943-66 (Box 58, Folder 1213-1214)
    Secretary, MLA
  - Parker, Wyman W., 1958-76 (Box 58, Folder 1215)
    Wesleyan librarian
  - Parker & Son, Ltd., 1938-39 (Box 58, Folder 1216)
  - Parks, George B., 1939-57 (Box 58, Folder 1217)
    Dryden, etc.
  - Parks, Stephen, 1961-71 (Box 58, Folder 1218-1219)
  - Parks, Stephen, 1972-76 (Box 59, Folder 1220-1222)
  - Parr, Johnstone, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 1223)
    Whythorne horoscope
  - Parsloe, G., 1937 (Box 59, Folder 1224)
    Oriel College, Oxford
  - Parsons, Robert W., 1941-43 (Box 59, Folder 1225)
    Wesleyan, Psi Opsilon
  - Patrick, Baxter, 1957-66 (Box 59, Folder 1226-1227)
    Wesleyan Alumni Association
  - Patrick, J. Max, 1950-64 (Box 59, Folder 1228)
  - Pattison, Walter T., 1947-50 (Box 59, Folder 1229)
    MLA, Committee on Photographic Reproductions
  - Paulson, Ronald, 1930-, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 1230)
    Hopkins, Yale, 18th century
  - Payne, John R., 1972-72 (Box 59, Folder 1231)
    University of Texas, Humanities Research Center
  - Pearce, Edward Holroyd Pearce, Baron, 1968-76 (Box 59, Folder 1232)
  - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1909-1975, 1940-73 (Box 59, Folder 1233)
  - Pearson, R. C., 1949-55 (Box 59, Folder 1234)
  - Periodical Index (Box 59, Folder 1235-1236)
  - Perrin, John C., 1894-, 1967-69 (Box 59, Folder 1237)
    Mahler, MS of 1st Symphony
  - Perry, Ten Eyck, 1966-67 (Box 59, Folder 1238)
    Yale friend
  - Peterson, Arthur W., 1969-70 (Box 59, Folder 1239)
    Holstein breeder
  - Peterson, Spiro, 1954-60 (Box 59, Folder 1240)
  - Petrea, Ion and Dina, 1969-76 (Box 59, Folder 1241)
  - Pettit, Henry, 1939-69 (Box 59, Folder 1242)
    University of Colorado, Young
  - Peyre, Henri M., 1940-76 (Box 59, Folder 1243)
    Yale French Department
  - Pforzheimer, Carl H., Jr., 1952-70 (Box 60, Folder 1244)
    Collector
  - Philip, Ian G., 1957-74 (Box 60, Folder 1245)
    Bodleian
  - Phillips, James E., 1960-74 (Box 60, Folder 1246)
    UCLA, Sidney
  - Pickering, Sir George, 1970-74 (Box 60, Folder 1247)
    Pembroke College, Oxford
  - Pickering & Chatto, Ltd., 1939-66 (Box 60, Folder 1248-1251)
  - Pierce, Henry H. and Mildred, 1964-74 (Box 60, Folder 1252)
    Manuscript Society and New Haven Free Public Library
  - The Pierpont Morgan Library, 1939-70 (Box 60, Folder 1253)
  - Pinto, Vivian de Sola, 1942-68 (Box 60, Folder 1254)
    University of Nottingham, Rochester, etc.
  - Piper, David Towry, 1918-, 1955-74 (Box 60, Folder 1255-1257)
  - Pitcher, Eleanor, 1944-59 (Box 60, Folder 1258)
  - Pitt, Harriet, 1965-71 (Box 60, Folder 1259)
  - Plomer, William, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 1260)
  - Plumb, John Harold, 1911-, 1951-71 (Box 61, Folder 1261)
    Christ's College, Cambridge, historian
  - Pollard, Graham, 1903-1976, 1936-57 (Box 61, Folder 1262)
    Bibliophile, bibliographer
  - Pollard, John A., 1956-65 (Box 61, Folder 1263)
    Council for Financial Aid to Education
  - Pomona College, 1941 (Box 61, Folder 1264)
    J. M. Osborn's candidacy for presidency, 1941
  - Pope, John Collins, 1963-76 (Box 61, Folder 1265)
  - Poole, H. Edmund, 1968-71 (Box 61, Folder 1266)
  - Porter, Quincy, b. 1897 and Lois, 1959-71 (Box 61, Folder 1267)
    Composer, Yale School of Music
  - Potter, Mabel H., 1963-72 (Box 61, Folder 1268)
    Friend of Evelyn Simpson
  - Pottle, Frederick A., 1937-74 (Box 61, Folder 1269)
    Yale English Department, Boswell
  - Powell, Lawrence Clark, 1952-76 (Box 61, Folder 1270)
    Director, Clark Library
  - Powell, Lawrence Fitzroy, 1881-1975, 1935-60 (Box 61, Folder 1271-1275)
    Johnsonian, Oxford
  - Powell, Lawrence Fitzroy, 1881-1975, 1960-75 (Box 62, Folder 1276-1280)
  - Powell, William C., 1941 (Box 62, Folder 1281)
  - Pratt, David H., 1967-68 (Box 62, Folder 1282)
  - Pratt, Robert A., 1940-64 (Box 62, Folder 1283)
    Chaucer, etc.
  - Prest, Harry, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 1284)
  - Preston, Jean, 1965-74 (Box 62, Folder 1285)
    Huntington Library, Curator of MSS, librarian, Osborn Collection, 1966-67
  - Preston, Kerrison, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 1286)
  - Price, Cecil, 1955-76 (Box 62, Folder 1287-1289)
  - Price, Douglas, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 1290)
  - Price, Hereward T., 1940-61 (Box 62, Folder 1291)
    Michigan, W. i. P., etc.
  - Price, R. M., 1957 (Box 62, Folder 1292)
  - Primitive Art, The Museum of (Robert Goldwater), 1959-60 (Box 62, Folder 1293)
  - Princeton University, 1944-62 (Box 62, Folder 1294)
  - Proffitt, Charles G., 1935-62 (Box 62, Folder 1295-1296)
  - Prouty, Charles T., 1951-72 (Box 62, Folder 1297)
  - Prown, Jules D., 1968-74 (Box 62, Folder 1298)
    Yale, History of Art, Director, Mellon Center
  - Pryor, Ruth, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 1299)
    Swansea, The Club
  - Purdy, Richard L., 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1300)
  - Putzel, Max, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 1301)
  - Quaritch, Bernard, Ltd., 1938-69 (Box 63, Folder 1302-1306)
  - Quennell, Peter, 1961 Apr 24 (Box 63, Folder 1307)
  - Quinlan, Maurice, 1939-72 (Box 63, Folder 1308)
    Boston College, Johnson
  - Quintana, Richard, 1952-70 (Box 63, Folder 1309)
    Wisconsin, Denham, etc.
  - Radzinowitz, Sir Leon, 1962-70 (Box 64, Folder 1310)
    Cambridge
  - Rahr, Gordon John, 1928-76 (Box 64, Folder 1311)
    Old friend from Wisconsin
  - Randall, Helen W., 1950-51 (Box 64, Folder 1312)
    Smith, English Inst.
  - Randolph, Mary Claire, 1941-42 (Box 64, Folder 1313)
  - Ratchford, Fannie, 1941-56 (Box 64, Folder 1314)
    University of Texas Library
  - Ratz, Erwin, 1959-61 (Box 64, Folder 1315)
  - Rawson, Claude J., 1961-72 (Box 64, Folder 1316)
    Newcastle-upon-Tyne, Warwick
  - Ray, Gordon N., 1961-73 (Box 64, Folder 1317)
    Guggenheim Foundation
  - Read, Allen Walker, 1938-56 (Box 64, Folder 1318)
    Chicago
  - Reade, Aleyn Lyell, 1952 (Box 64, Folder 1319)
  - Reed, Charles, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 1320)
    Friend in Lebanon
  - Rees-Mogg, William, 1967-68 (Box 64, Folder 1321)
    Editor, The Times (London)
  - Renaissance Quarterly, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 1322)
    Sidney article
  - The Renaissance Society of America, 1961-68 (Box 64, Folder 1323)
  - Rendell, Kenneth W., 1967-68 (Box 64, Folder 1324)
  - Rhodes, Richard, 1959-70 (Box 64, Folder 1325)
    Yale undergraduate friend
  - Rhodes, Virginia V., 1971-73 (Box 64, Folder 1326)
  - Ribeiro, Alvaro F. V., 1971-76 (Box 64, Folder 1327)
    J. M. Osborn's research assistant, 1971-74, Burney
  - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1965-67 (Box 64, Folder 1328)
    Senator
  - Rice, Warner Grenelle, 1942-62 (Box 64, Folder 1329)
    University of Michigan, travel literature
  - Richards, Paul C., 1963-67 (Box 64, Folder 1330)
  - Richardson, Colin, 1954-57 (Box 64, Folder 1331)
  - Ricks, Christopher, 1963-67 (Box 64, Folder 1332)
    Tennyson
  - Rickword, D. R., 1951-52 (Box 64, Folder 1333)
  - Riddell, Jean (Montgomery) and Richard J., 1939-75 (Box 64, Folder 1334-1336)
    Sister-in-law
  - Rider, Fremont, 1937-50 (Box 64, Folder 1337)
  - Rieley, John Cabell, 1945- and Elizabeth Dumesnil (Gawthrop), 1945-, 1970-76 (Box 65, Folder 1338)
  - Ringler, William A., 1941-73 (Box 65, Folder 1339)
    Chicago, Sidney
  - Ringrose, C. W., 1954-56 (Box 65, Folder 1340)
    Lincoln's Inn, librarian
  - Ripley, S. Dillon, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 1341)
    Director, Smithsonian
  - Ritchie, Andrew Carnduff, 1959-70 (Box 65, Folder 1342)
    Director, Yale University Art Gallery
  - Robbins, Caroline, 1960-64 (Box 65, Folder 1343)
    Bryn Mawr College, Marvell
  - Robbins, Rossell Hope, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 1344)
    Middle English rolls
  - Roberts, Colin, 1958-72 (Box 65, Folder 1345)
    Clarendon Press
  - Roberts, F. Warren, 1971-75 (Box 65, Folder 1346)
  - Roberts, R. Julian, 1962-76 (Box 65, Folder 1347)
    Bibliographical Society, British Museum
  - Roberts, Sir Sydney Castle, 1887-1966, 1944-65 (Box 65, Folder 1348)
    Cambridge, Johnson, etc.
  - Robertson, Marjorie C., 1937-39 (Box 65, Folder 1349)
  - Robinson, Fred C., 1970-76 (Box 65, Folder 1350)
  - Robinson, Lionel K. and Philip R. (William H. Robinson Ltd.), 1952-57 (Box 65, Folder 1351)
  - Roche, John Patrick, 1964-73 (Box 65, Folder 1352-1353)
    J. M. Osborn's research assistant, 1965-67
  - Rochow, Elizabeth (Cook), 1910-, 1951-76 (Box 65, Folder 1354)
    Research assistant, Spence
  - Rogers, Arthur, 1938-61 (Box 65, Folder 1355-1356)
  - Rogers, Brian D., 1975-76 (Box 65, Folder 1357)
    Librarian, Connecticut College
  - Rogers, Robert W., 1954-76 (Box 65, Folder 1358-1359)
    University of Illinois, 18th century
  - Rogers, Rutherford David, 1970-76 (Box 65, Folder 1360)
    Yale University librarian
  - Rollins, Carl Purington, 1880-1960 and Margaret, 1939-70 (Box 66, Folder 1361-1363)
    Printer to Yale University
  - Roscioni, Gian Carlo, 1961-72 (Box 66, Folder 1364-1365)
    Italian scholar who could not obtain visa to be J. M. Osborn's research assistant
  - Rose, Alfred, 1968-71 (Box 66, Folder 1366)
    Mahler MS of Das Klagende Lied
  - The Rosenbach Company, 1940-41 (Box 66, Folder 1367)
  - Rosenthal, Albi, 1954-73 (Box 66, Folder 1368)
  - Ross, Angus Macfarlane, 1950-66 (Box 66, Folder 1369)
    Arbuthnot
  - Ross, E. Patricia, 1940 (Box 66, Folder 1370)
  - Ross, Ian, 1965-73 (Box 66, Folder 1371)
    Kames
  - Rosseter, Alice, 1937-40 (Box 66, Folder 1372)
  - Rota, Bertram, 1968 Jul 2 (Box 66, Folder 1373)
  - Rousseau, George S., 1966-70 (Box 66, Folder 1374)
  - Rowse, Alfred Leslie, 1903-, 1970-74 (Box 66, Folder 1375)
    Sidney, etc., All Souls, Oxford
  - Royal Society of Arts, 1962-69 (Box 66, Folder 1376)
  - Rudkin, Margaret, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 1377)
    Mrs. Delany
  - Ruhe, Edward L., 1947-71 (Box 66, Folder 1378)
    Rutgers, Kansas, Spence, Johnson, etc.
  - Ruoff, A. LaVonne Prasher, 1963-71 (Box 66, Folder 1379)
  - Russell, Doris A., 1946 (Box 66, Folder 1380)
  - Russell, Norma, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1381)
    Crabbe
  - Rutter, William, 1950-51 (Box 66, Folder 1382)
    Michigan State College Press
  - The John Rylands Library, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 1383)
  - Ryskamp, Charles Andrew, 1928-, 1954-76 (Box 66, Folder 1384)
    Princeton, Morgan Library, Cooper, Sidney
  - Sadler, Ernest A., 1935-44 (Box 67, Folder 1385)
    Dr. Taylor's house, Derbyshire
  - St. Catherine's College, Oxford, 1936-68 (Box 67, Folder 1386)
  - Sale, William M., 1940-42 (Box 67, Folder 1387)
  - Salloch, William, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 1388)
  - Salop, County of, County Record Office, 1952-57 (Box 67, Folder 1389)
  - Salwey, Roger, 1937-41 (Box 67, Folder 1390)
  - Sambrook, A. James, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1391)
    Warton and Malone
  - Sanders of Oxford Ltd., 1960-66 (Box 67, Folder 1392)
  - Santos, Maria Boaventura de Sousa, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 1393)
    Fulbright student
  - Sappington, Olga and Joan, 1947-48 (Box 67, Folder 1394)
  - Sargeant, Howland H., 1935-65 (Box 67, Folder 1395)
  - Sauls, Richard Lynn, 1966-68 (Box 67, Folder 1396)
  - Sawyer, Charles J., Ltd., 1951-65 (Box 67, Folder 1397)
  - Sawyer, Robert Graham, 1911-, 1934-52 (Box 67, Folder 1398-1402)
    J. M. Osborn's research assistant, 1946-47, periodical index, Work in Progress
  - Sawyer, Roland, 1970-71 (Box 67, Folder 1403)
  - Sayce, Richard A., 1957-74 (Box 67, Folder 1404)
    Worcester College librarian, Oxford
  - Schilling, Bernard N., 1956-76 (Box 67, Folder 1405)
    University of Rochester, Dryden, Whythorne, etc.
  - Schless, Howard H., 1961-74 (Box 67, Folder 1406)
    Columbia, POAS, Dryden, etc.
  - Schmitz, R. M., 1952-61 (Box 67, Folder 1407)
    Washington University, St. Louis, Pope
  - Schoenbaum, Samuel, 1963-69 (Box 67, Folder 1408)
    Northwestern, Shakespeare, etc.
  - Scholes, Percy Alfred, 1877-1958, 1952-54 (Box 67, Folder 1409)
  - Schoolcraft, John S., d. 1966, and Dorothy, 1939-66 (Box 67, Folder 1410)
    Writer, fund-raiser, friend
  - Schroder, John, 1954-55 (Box 67, Folder 1411)
  - Scientific Library Service, 1964-65 (Box 67, Folder 1412)
  - Scott, Florence, 1941-60 (Box 68, Folder 1413)
  - Scott-Craig, T. S. K., 1946 (Box 68, Folder 1414)
    Dartmouth
  - Scoufas, Alice-Lyle, 1972-76 (Box 68, Folder 1415)
    California State, Fullerton, Shakespeare, Braye Lute Book, Huntington
  - Scouten, Arthur H., 1950-55 (Box 68, Folder 1416)
    University of Pennsylvania
  - Scranton, William W., 1973 Oct 5 (Box 68, Folder 1417)
  - Scribner's Sons, Charles, 1955-72 (Box 68, Folder 1418)
  - Sedge, Douglas, 1964-65 (Box 68, Folder 1419)
    Candidate for research assistant
  - Sedgwick, Maria, 1966-72 (Box 68, Folder 1420)
    Widow of Romney
  - Seed, Allen H., Jr., 1958-65 (Box 68, Folder 1421)
  - Seelig, Sharon C., 1975 (Box 68, Folder 1422)
    Mt. Holyoke, Traherne
  - Seitz, Robert W., 1937 (Box 68, Folder 1423)
  - Sellar, Margaret, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1424)
    Handlyng Synne
  - Seluzicki, Charles J., 1970 (Box 68, Folder 1425)
  - Sencourt, Robert, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 1426)
  - Seng, Peter J., 1957-67 (Box 68, Folder 1427)
    Connecticut College, 16th and 17th century poetry, Braye Lute Book
  - Sessler, Charles, Inc., 1961 (Box 68, Folder 1428)
  - Sewall, Richard, 1950-73 (Box 68, Folder 1429)
  - Sexton, George, Ltd., 1956-63 (Box 68, Folder 1430)
  - Seymour, Charles, Jr., 1963-70 (Box 68, Folder 1431)
    Yale clubs
  - Shaaber, Matthew A., 1941-62 (Box 68, Folder 1432)
  - Shackleton, Robert, 1919-, 1955-76 (Box 68, Folder 1433-1438)
    Brasenose College, Oxford, Bodleian librarian
  - Shapiro, I. A., 1956-75 (Box 68, Folder 1439)
    Cornell, Oxford
  - Sherbo, Arthur, 1954-73 (Box 69, Folder 1440)
    Michigan State
  - Shepard, Brooks, Jr., 1954-63 (Box 69, Folder 1441)
  - Sherburn, George Wiley, 1884-1962, 1935-62 (Box 69, Folder 1442-1449)
    Columbia and Harvard, Pope and Spence, J. M. Osborn's mentor
  - Shestack, Alan, 1973-76 (Box 70, Folder 1450)
    Director, Yale Art Gallery
  - Shields, The Honorable Joseph F. G., 1965-68 (Box 70, Folder 1451)
    Irish ambassador to Italy
  - Shipman, Arthur L., Jr., 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1452)
  - Short, John D., Jr., 1966-71 (Box 70, Folder 1453)
    Oxford and L. F. Powell
  - Short, Raymond W., 1940-62 (Box 70, Folder 1454)
    Academic friend
  - Simmons, John S. G., 1959-71 (Box 70, Folder 1455)
  - Simpson, Claude M., Jr., 1974-75 (Box 70, Folder 1456)
  - Simpson, Percy and Evelyn, 1934-64 (Box 70, Folder 1457)
    Oxford, Donne, etc.
  - Sims, G. F., 1954-61 (Box 70, Folder 1458)
  - Sires, Mary, 1949-75 (Box 70, Folder 1459-1460)
    J. M. Osborn's irreplaceable secretary for many years
  - Sisson, Charles J., 1941-44 (Box 70, Folder 1461)
    MHRA and Work in Progress
  - Sister Mary Ignatia, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 1462)
  - Sister Thomas Marion, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 1463)
  - Sizer, Theodore, 1956-66 (Box 70, Folder 1464)
  - Sluberski, Thomas, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 1465)
  - Smart, John H., 1947-52 (Box 70, Folder 1466)
    Holstein breeding
  - Smith, Carlton Sprague, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 1467)
  - Smith, David Nichol, 1875-1962, 1934-62 (Box 70, Folder 1468)
    Oxford, Dryden, Malone, etc.
  - Smith, Hugh F., 1941 (Box 70, Folder 1469)
  - Smith, John Harrington, 1952-55 (Box 70, Folder 1470)
  - Smith, Joseph H., 1939-40 (Box 70, Folder 1471)
    Lee papers
  - Smith, Milton S., 1941-56 (Box 70, Folder 1472)
  - Smith, Robert M., 1948 (Box 70, Folder 1473)
  - Smith, Simon Nowell, 1963-75 (Box 70, Folder 1474)
    Bibliographical Society
  - Smith, Warren Hunting, 1954-68 (Box 70, Folder 1475)
    Walpole, etc.
  - Snyder, Henry L., 1964-75 (Box 70, Folder 1476)
    University of Kansas, Marlborough correspondence, newsletters
  - Somervell, Diana, 1965-66 (Box 70, Folder 1477)
  - Soskin, Moussia, d. 1962, 1958-62 (Box 70, Folder 1478)
    Banking, etc., etc.
  - Sotheby & Co., 1938-65 (Box 70, Folder 1479)
  - Sowers, Roy Vernon, 1954-64 (Box 70, Folder 1480)
  - Sparrow, John Hanburg, 1906-, 1957-76 (Box 71, Folder 1481)
    Warden, All Souls College, Oxford
  - Spelman, Henry B., 1946 (Box 71, Folder 1482)
  - Spencer, Terence J. B., 1963-74 (Box 71, Folder 1483)
    University of Birmingham, Shakespeare
  - Spiller, Robert E., 1939 (Box 71, Folder 1484)
    Swarthmore, MLA paper
  - Spindler, John L. and Esther, 1957-73 (Box 71, Folder 1485)
  - Stainer, R. S., 1956 (Box 71, Folder 1486)
    Magdalen College School, Oxford, Whythorne
  - Stanley, Eric, 1975-76 (Box 71, Folder 1487)
  - Stanlis, Peter J., 1960-61 (Box 71, Folder 1488)
    Burke Newsletter
  - Starlight Festival of Music, 1955-68 (Box 71, Folder 1489)
  - Stauffer, Donald A., 1937-38 (Box 71, Folder 1490)
    Princeton, Oxford friend
  - Stead, Julian, Dom, 1941-74 (Box 71, Folder 1491)
    William Force Stead (father)
  - Sternfeld, Frederick W., 1957-68 (Box 71, Folder 1492)
  - Stevens, Halsey, 1967-73 (Box 71, Folder 1493)
    USC, music
  - Stevens, Holly, 1972-73 (Box 71, Folder 1494)
    Daughter of Wallace Stevens
  - Stevens, Paul P., 1935 (Box 71, Folder 1495)